netprospex.com 2015-10-16

# Privacy Policy | NetProspex

##### **Effective as of October 3, 2014**

NetProspex Inc. is serious about protecting the privacy of your personal information, whether you are a customer or subscriber to or user of any of the NetProspex on-line services, or a visitor to or user of the NetProspex website. We have put strict policies into place to ensure that the privacy of your personal information is protected while still enabling you to make use of the website or the on-line services provided by NetProspex. We use information collected about you through the use of our on-line services or on the website solely for the purposes set out in this policy. The terms of this privacy policy may be updated from time to time, so please check our website or this page occasionally for updates. The terms of this policy are also incorporated into the NetProspex Terms of Use, found at <http://www.netprospex.com/terms-of-use>.

##### **Collection of Information and its use**

When you sign up with NetProspex on-line, either in the form of a subscription to a NetProspex on-line service, or by requesting additional information about our services on our website, or by signing up to participate in a NetProspex survey, event, contest or sweepstakes on-line, all users are asked to fill out a registration form. Registration information is kept private and secure and is used only for purposes of maintaining subscription accounts, billing and to contact users with information regarding our services (including newsletters, whitepapers, and eBooks), surveys, contests or similar events. We do not share, sell or rent this information with or to any third party. NetProspex employs a secure e-mail hosting service to deliver e-mail and communications.

By completing any of our on-line registration processes, you are specifically agreeing to receive communication from us by e-mail, postal mail and by telephone.

In addition to the personal information added by users in this registration process, other information collected will include (and is not limited to) IP address, browser type, time and date of use, and any activity performed while on our website or using our service. By using our website and/or by registering with NetProspex for informational, subscription service purposes or any other on-line purposes, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described herein by NetProspex.

PLEASE NOTE: Your registration information and/or any information collected by NetProspex when you visit the NetProspex website, is neither added to the NetProspex Content (as defined in the Terms of Use) within the Services, nor is it included in the NetProspex Business Contact Database (see the description of such database below) and such information cannot be accessed by users of a NetProspex service. If you wish to share contact information with other users of the NetProspex services you may use the separate user content contribution service, terms for which are found at: /termsofusecontent for adding contact information to the NetProspex database.

##### **Personal Information and its use**

Personal Information Collected from Website Users, Subscribers and Information Submitted to Register for NetProspex Services.

NetProspex will not sell, rent, license or otherwise share your Personally Information (such as your name, email, mail address, and billing address) that you submit in your registration or subscription for our services or your registration for inquiries into our services.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected from Website Users and Subscribers

In order to make NetProspex services more useful to customers, we may, from time to time, collect and analyze aggregated, non-personal, statistical information about subscribers and visitors. From time to time we may also share this Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) in aggregate and de-identified form only, with third parties. This information reveals nothing about individual users and visitors to the website and is only used to communicate demographic and behavioral understandings of our customers and visitors internally and to potential advertisers, business partners and investors.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information Collected from the NetProspex Business Contact Database

If your business data appears in the NetProspex Business Contact Database (as described below), NetProspex may share such information with a third party provider for the purpose of extracting certain Non-PII information, such as demographic, behavioral and technical information from such data to aggregate and create segments of anonymous data, which are also called “cookies,” that can be used for targeted business ads and for marketing purposes. Such extracted, anonymous, and aggregated Non-PII information may be shared with third party partners such as ad networks, data management platforms, and others to help them present, better target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and online marketing efforts. Specifically, NetProspex partners with Liveramp for the purposes of providing certain of our third party partners with non-PII data cookies from our NetProspex Business Contact Database which can be used for the purpose of online advertising and marketing. Further information on Liveramp can be found at: <http://liveramp.com/privacy/>

To opt out of the use of your Non-PII information for data targeting and advertising purposes as described here, please contact us via email: [support@netprospex.com](mailto:support@netprospex.com) or [privacy@netprospex.com](mailto:privacy@netprospex.com), via the internet: [http://support.netprospex.com](http://support.netprospex.com/), or via a toll-free number to our Customer Service: 1-888-826-4877.

To learn more about the use of Non-PII cookies for advertising purposes please go to the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), and to opt out of third party data collection and targeting by third parties please view this link: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>. In addition, the Direct Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) publishes its opt-out program at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

##### **The NetProspex Business Contact Database and Opt Out**

The NetProspex Business Contact Database contains millions of business contact records and company profiles. The NetProspex Business Contact Database has been created by NetProspex in the following ways: 1) by way of crowd-sourcing, meaning that data or content has been contributed to the database by third parties, as further described in our User Content Contribution Terms of Use and 2) by way of licensing of business information from third party data providers. The NetProspex Business Contact Database is cleaned and verified by way of NetProspex’s proprietary CleneStep™ methods and technologies and is then made available to our customers, partners and other third parties via a variety of contractual means, including to users of the website through on-line subscription services.

The NetProspex Business Contact Database contains business information only. The NetProspex Business Contact Database does not identify the source of the underlying information within the database or to third parties. If you wish to update your business profile or request the removal of your profile from the NetProspex Business Contact Database, you may do so at any time, via email: [support@netprospex.com](mailto:support@netprospex.com) or [privacy@netprospex.com](mailto:privacy@netprospex.com), via the internet: [http://support.netprospex.com](http://support.netprospex.com/), or via a toll-free number to our Customer Service: 1-888-826-4877. NetProspex will remove your business contact information promptly upon any opt-out request.

##### **Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information collected on or through our website and in our services. While we use the latest security technologies and tools it should be noted that no method of electronic storage or transmission can guarantee absolute security.

When you enter sensitive personally identifiable information (such as credit card information) into our system, such information is stored in an encrypted form (with Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology) on our servers and will not be sold or shared with any third party other than the trusted transaction processing partner that we use to complete any on-line financial transaction.

While we strive to protect your personal information, NetProspex cannot ensure or warrant the security of any data or content you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your personal information, we will notify you as soon as possible so you can take appropriate protective steps and to inform you of the steps that NetProspex is taking with respect to such breach.

##### **Use of cookies**

NetProspex uses “cookies” (cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive) to store some non-sensitive personal preference information regarding your use of the website for future visits and to enhance the NetProspex services. Cookies allow us to recognize you more quickly and provide a more personalized and productive experience. Our use of cookies in this manner is similar to that used on most major websites. You may decline the use of cookies and configure your browser to accept, reject, or erase all cookies or be notified when a cookie is set. To do so, send an email to [support@netprospex.com](mailto:support@netprospex.com) or call us at 1-888-826-4877.

##### **Communication with our subscribers**

We communicate with subscribers to our services through e-mail. We do not share or sell your registration information for marketing purposes, however we will communicate with customers or subscribers in accordance with such customer or subscriber preferences.

Users may choose to opt out of receiving e-mail communications from NetProspex and clear opt-out instructions are included in e-mail messages, or you can simply send an email to [support@netprospex.com](mailto:support@netprospex.com) or call us at 1-888-826-4877. However, we periodically communicate information to active customers about customer accounts, renewal notices and information about service changes in order to ensure the integrity of our services and such communications cannot be terminated by subscribers unless they cease to subscribe to the services.

##### **Links to other sites**

We include links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. This policy applies to information collected by us through the website or in the provision of the services we offer.

##### **Children**

NetProspex is a business information site providing contact information on working professionals. NetProspex is not targeted, intended or expected to be of use to children. User provided contributions of content or contact information regarding or about children are expressly prohibited.

##### **Contact Us**

NetProspex Inc.  
Attn: Customer Support  
300 Third Ave  
Waltham, MA 02451  
Phone: 888-826-4877  
E-mail: [privacy@netprospex.com](mailto:privacy@netprospex.com)

Customer Support hours: between 8am and 6pm Eastern Standard Time.

##### **Feedback**

We welcome your comments on this Privacy Policy on our Contact Us page. For more information about NetProspex see our website.

##### **Modification of this policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time in the future and we recommend that users and subscribers check this site frequently. Any changes made will be effective immediately upon posting an update of this Privacy Policy to this website. Any changes of a material nature in this Privacy Policy will be communicated to you here, and by notice of the update on the homepage of our website. .

Last update to this Privacy Policy, October 3, 2014 (updating the Privacy Policy dated April 16, 2013), adding section on additional use by NetProspex of Non-PII from NetProspex Business Contact Database for third party advertising purposes, and other minor updates.
